A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Meeting records, 2010-2013., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2012 Dec 10. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2013 July 18. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2012 Nov 26. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Jan 4. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Jan 9. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Feb 13. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Mar 13. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Apr 10. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 May 8. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 June 19. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Veterans Working Group, 2013 Aug 14. (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Series VII. Project files - Fort Monroe Authority, 2010-2013., Extent: .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  Project files: Fort Monroe Authority, 2010-2013, are arranged alphabetically and include Board of Directors meeting records, correspondence, deeds, financial records, manuals, maps, photographs, plans, and reports. Located along the Chesapeake Bay within the city limits of Hampton, Fort Monroe was an Army base that was designated for closure pursuant to the 2005 Defense Base Closure and Realignment Commission Report. When the base closed, the land, buildings, and infrastructure assets transferred to the Commonwealth and this necessitated a redevelopment and reuse plan. The Fort Monroe Federal Area Development Authority (FMFADA), a political subdivision of the Commonwealth of Virginia and local redevelopment authority, was established to determine how best to manage the historic resources, preserve and protect the open space, and ensure the economic sustainability at Fort Monroe. In 2010, an act of the General Assembly established the Fort Monroe Authority which was charged with the responsibility of reuse planning and management of the area.
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Manual (Part I), 2011. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Manual (Part II), 2011. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors meeting, 2010 June 24. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors meeting, 2010 Nov 18. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Executive Committee meeting, 2010 Dec 9. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors meeting, 2011 Jan 6. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Executive Committee meeting, 2011 Apr 22. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Workshop, 2010 Sept 30. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Board of Directors - Workshop, 2010 Oct 21. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Correspondence, 2011-2012. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Financial statements, 2011-2012. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Historic Preservation Manual and Design Standard, 2012 Mar 10. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Maps and photographs, 2010-2012. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Proclamation, 2012. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Quit Claim Deed (Draft), 2013. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Report, undated. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Report, undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Reuse Plan, 2008 Aug 20. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Transition Discussion meeting, 2012 May 1. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Fort Monroe Authority: Transition Plan Memorandum of Understanding (draft), undated. (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Series VIII. Subject files, 2010-2013., Extent: .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  Subject files, 2010-2013, are arranged alphabetically and document topics of interest to the Secretary, such as homeland security, veterans, and the Wounded Warrior Program. Files may include correspondence, reports, and studies.
  - BRAC Analysis, 2010. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Homeland Security Evaluation Program, 2011-2013. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Gap Analysis Report - Hampton Roads, 2010 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Grant Satisfaction Survey Results, 2010 July. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Homeland Security grants, 2010. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Legislative impact analysis (Office of Commonwealth Preparedness Assessment), 2006 July 31. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Logistics Support Staff (NOVA Regional Public Safety Logistics Support Staff), 2011 Apr. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Long-term Care Feasibility Study - Quality Care Earned (Dept. of Veterans Services), 2007 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Meeting the Memorial Needs of Virginia Veterans, 2007 Nov. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Review of Homeland Security Funding and Preparedness in Virginia (JLARC), 2005. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Student Leadership Forum, 2010. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - TRICARE Overview, 2012 Oct 5. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Updating Hampton Roads Homeland Security Strategy, 2010 July 26. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Work, School or Home? Issues in Sheltering in Place During an Emergency, 2011. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Wounded Warrior Program - Virginia Tech Needs Assessment, 2010. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Wounded Warrior Program, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 4)